queensnake.com 2018-08-25

# Queensnake.com - Privacy Policy

**Preamble and General Principles**

The following information is designed to help you understand how we collect, use, disseminate and safeguard the information you provide to us while accessing and using our Site. If you do not agree with our information practices, please do not access or use our Site. By accessing and using our Site, you signify your assent to this Privacy Policy.  
This Privacy Policy describes how Queensnake.com collects information from all Users (Visitors: who access some parts of our websites but do not have accounts and Members: who pay fees to gain access to the website), what we do with the information we collect. We request that you read this Privacy Policy carefully. 

**Revisions to this Policy**

Queensnake.com reserves the right to revise, amend, or modify this policy and our other policies and agreements at any time and in any manner. The user should periodically check for any modifications of this Policy by re-visiting this web page and using the "refresh" button on the user's browser. 

**About this privacy policy**

This privacy policy explains how we (Queensnake.com) collect, use, share and transfer your personal data when you use our services. 

Personal data is any information about you by which you can be identified. This can include information such as: 

  * email address
  * information about your device (such as the IP address, which is a numerical code to identify your device that can provide information about the country, region or city where you are based)
  * information relating to your personal circumstances and how you use our sites, apps and services

Sometimes our sites may contain links to third party sites and services. These sites and services have their own privacy policies. If you follow a link to a third party, you should read the privacy policy shown on their site. 

**What personal data we collect and how we use it**

We collect personal data when you sign up for our services and when you browse our site. This information is used to provide our services and analyse how visitors use our site. 

When you sign up for an account on Queensnake.com we collect: 

  * your email address

When you sign up for a Queensnake.com account, we assign you a unique ID number that we use to recognise you when you are signed in to our services.  When you use our site we may also use cookies or similar technology to collect extra data, including: 

  * your IP address - a numerical code to identify your device and which can provide information about the country, region or city where you are based
  * your browsing history of the content you have visited on our sites, including information on how you were referred to our sites via another website
  * details of your devices, for example, the unique device ID, unique advertising ID and browsers used to access our content

**How we collect personal data**

We collect personal data when you: 

  * sign up to our site
  * access our sites, through cookies and other similar technology
  * when you contact us via email

**Why we use your personal data**

We use personal data for a number of purposes, including the following: 

  * help you resetting your password
  * for internal administrative purposes - such as our accounting and records
  * For statistical purposes such as analysing the performance of our sites and apps and to understand how visitors use them
  * To respond to your queries and to resolve complaints
  * For security and fraud prevention, and to ensure that our sites and apps are safe and secure and used in line with our terms of use
  * To comply with applicable laws and regulations

**Legal grounds for using your personal data**

We will only use your personal data where we have a legal ground to do so. We determine the legal grounds based on the purposes for which we have collected and used your personal data. In every case, the legal ground will be one of the following: 

  * Consent: For example, where you have allowed to use cookies
  * Our legitimate interests: For example, we will rely on our legitimate interest when we analyse what content has been viewed on our sites
  * Performance of a contract with you: For example, where you have purchased a subscription from us and we need to use your contact details in order to process your order and deliver your subscription
  * Compliance with law: In some cases, we may have a legal obligation to use or keep your personal data

**Updating your personal data and your profile page on our sites**

When you sign up for an account, you have access to your profile page. Under "account" (cogwheel icon) you can review your information and preferences. You can also update your information or preferences if you want. 

**Security of your personal data**

We have implemented appropriate technical and organisational controls to protect your personal data against unauthorised processing and against accidental loss, damage or destruction. You are responsible for choosing a secure password when we ask you to set up a password to access parts of our site. You should keep this password confidential and you should choose a password that you do not use on any other site. You should not share your password with anyone else, including anyone who works for us. Unfortunately, sending information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data once with us, we cannot guarantee the security of any personal data sent to our site while still in transit and so you provide it at your own risk. 

**Who we share your personal data with**

We do not share your personal data with other people or organisations that are not directly linked to us except under the following circumstances: 

  * We may share your data with other organisations that provide services on our behalf such as dealing with online payments and other forms of payment processing, ie credit card transactions and preventing fraud
  * We may also share your data with our advertising partners, as set out in the section about Online Advertising below
  * We may reveal your personal data to any law enforcement agency, court, regulator, government authority or other organisation if we are required to do so to meet a legal or regulatory obligation, or otherwise to protect our rights or the rights of anyone else
  * We may reveal your personal data to any other organisation that buys, or to which we transfer all, or substantially all, of our assets and business. If this sale or transfer takes place, we will use reasonable efforts to try to make sure that the organisation we transfer your personal data to uses it in line with our privacy policy

We will not share your personal data with anyone else for their own marketing purposes. 

**International data transfers**

Data we collect may be transferred to, stored and processed in any country or territory where one or more of our service providers are based or have facilities. While other countries or territories may not have the same standards of data protection as those in your home country, we will continue to protect personal data that we transfer in line with this privacy policy.  Whenever we transfer your personal data out of the European Economic Area (EEA), we ensure similar protection and put in place at least one of these safeguards: 

  * We will only transfer your personal data to countries that have been found to provide an adequate level of protection for personal data.
  * We may also use specific approved contracts with our service providers that are based in countries outside the EEA. These contracts give your personal data the same protection it has in the EEA .
  * Where we use service providers in the United States, we may transfer personal data to them if they are part of the Privacy Shield scheme, which requires them to provide a similar level of protection of your personal data to what is required in the EEA.

**How long we keep your personal data**

We keep your personal data for only as long as we need to. How long we need you personal data depends on what we are using it for, as set out in this privacy policy. For example, we may need to use it to answer your queries about a product or service and as a result may keep personal data while you are still using our product or services. We may also need to keep your personal data for accounting purposes, for example, where you have bought a subscription. If we no longer need your data, we will delete it or make it anonymous by removing all details that identify you. If we have asked for your permission to process your personal data and we have no other lawful grounds to continue with that processing, and you withdraw your permission, we will delete your personal data. 

**How we may contact you**

_Service communications_

From time to time we may send you service emails, for example, telling you your subscription is coming to an end or thanking you when you contribute or place an order with us. 

_Marketing communications newsletters_

If we have your permission, we may send you materials we think may interest you. Depending on your marketing preferences, this may be by email. You can decide not to receive these emails at any time and will be able to "unsubscribe" directly by clicking a link in the email or through your email preferences in the tab "Newsletter" when you are signed in to your account. 

_Responding to your queries or complaints_

If you have raised a query or a complaint with us, we may contact you to answer your query or to resolve your complaint. 

**Cookies and similar technology**

When you visit our site we may collect personal data from you automatically using cookies or similar technology. A cookie is a small file that can be placed on your device that allows us to recognise and remember you.  This privacy policy includes our [cookie policy](https://queensnake.com/cookiepolicy), where you can find details of our key advertising partners. 

**Online advertising**

We do not collect or use information such as your name, email address, postal address or phone number for personalised online advertising. 

When you browse our sites or use our apps, some of the cookies and similar technology we place on your device are advertising cookies. 

We may also share online data collected through cookies and similar technology with our advertising partners. This means that when you are on another website, you may be shown advertising based on your browsing patterns on our site. 

**Advertising that we place on our site or on other sites**

We also use online advertising to promote our own products and services. This means that you may see advertising for our products and services on our sites and when you are on other, third party websites, including social media platforms. 

**Your rights with regard to the personal data that we hold about you**

You can contact us with regard to the following rights in relation to your personal data: 

  * If you would like to have a copy of the personal data we hold on you or if you think that we hold incorrect personal data about you, please email **support@queensnake.com**. We will deal with requests for copies of your personal data or for correction of your personal data within one month. If your request is complicated or if you have made a large number of requests, it may take us longer. We will let you know if we need longer than one month to respond. You will not have to pay a fee to obtain a copy of your personal data (or to exercise any of the other rights). However, we may charge a reasonable fee if your request is clearly unfounded, repetitive or excessive
  * Where you have provided us with consent to use your personal data, you can withdraw this at any time
  * Where applicable, you may also have a right to receive a machine-readable copy of your personal data
  * You also have the right to ask us to delete your personal data or restrict how it is used. There may be exceptions to the right to erasure for specific legal reasons which, if applicable, we will set out for you in response to your request. Where applicable, you have the right to object to processing of your personal data for certain purposes
  * If you want to make any of these requests, please contact **support@queensnake.com**.

We may need to request specific information from you to help us confirm your identity. 

**Personal Information**

Queensnake.com collects information from Users who access the various parts of our website. We use this information to provide a customized experience as you use our website and do not share this information with third parties. However, we may disclose personal information collected when we believe that such disclosure is required by law. 

**Registration**

Members are asked to provide certain personal information when they sign up for our website including name, address, telephone number, billing information (such as a credit card number). The personal information collected from Members during the registration process is used to manage each Member's account (such as for billing purposes). This information is collected by our credit card processors/billing companies, and is not shared with third parties, unless specifically stated otherwise or in special circumstances. 

**Email Inquiries**

When Users send email inquiries to us, the return email address is used to answer the email inquiry we receive. We does not use the return email address for any other purpose and does not share the return email address with any third party. 

**Internet Data**

We collect IP addresses, referral URLs, browser preferences. This information is used internally to track how users come to be referred to our Site for the purpose of compensating our affiliates, advertisers, and other marketing entities. This information is not shared to third-parties. We never discloses any customer-specific information to third parties unless it is reasonable to believe that doing so is required by law, a binding contract, a Court Order, or other state, local, or administrative regulation. 

**E-mail list**

You will have the option to join our mailing list. If you choose to join the mailing list, your email address will be stored in our database and used periodically to send you news and promotions about our website. You can be removed from the list by following the link contained in the email instructing you on how to unsubscribe. Every email we send you will have a link contained therein which will direct you to a site where you can unsubscribe. These unsubscribe links, when clicked, will automatically remove your email address from our database without any additional action on your part. 

**Children's Protection**

Our sites are designed for adults, but not for use by anyone under the age of 18. We make every effort to ensure that our website contain adequate warnings to make our content obvious and to warn users under the age of 18 that they are not welcome to view our website. 

**Data Security**

We make every effort to ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, however we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent "hackers" from illegally obtaining information. 

**Questions about Our Privacy Policy**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices described herein, you may contact our support at **support@queensnake.com**
